{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "prompt": "What special prop should always be included for lists of elements?",
      "answers": [
        "id",
        "name",
        "key",
        "prop"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "prompt": "A React component is a function that returns ______.",
      "answers": [
        "HTML",
        "JSX",
        "props",
        "state"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sdcsdcs",
      "answers": [
        "dsds",
        "sdsd",
        "sdssd",
        "ddd"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sdcsdcs",
      "answers": [
        "dsds",
        "sdsd",
        "sdssd",
        "ddd"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sdcsdcs",
      "answers": [
        "dsds",
        "sdsd",
        "sdssd",
        "ddd"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sdcsdcs",
      "answers": [
        "dsds",
        "sdsd",
        "sdssd",
        "ddd"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sdcsdcs",
      "answers": [
        "dsds",
        "sdsd",
        "sdssd",
        "ddd"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sdcsdcs",
      "answers": [
        "dsds",
        "sdsd",
        "sdssd",
        "ddd"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sdcsdcs",
      "answers": [
        "dsds",
        "sdsd",
        "sdssd",
        "ddd"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sdcsdcs",
      "answers": [
        "dsds",
        "sdsd",
        "sdssd",
        "ddd"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "prompt": "sdcsdcs",
      "answers": [
        "dsds",
        "sdsd",
        "sdssd",
        "ddd"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 11
    }
  ]
}